Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, Photograph Albums
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, photograph albums
circa 1920-1968
SC0227
Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation.
30 Linear feet (61 volumes)
Volumes include black and white photographs of Stanford sports including football, baseball, basketball, track, golf, tennis, swimming. Where indicated, some albums contain clippings only.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Volumes include black and white photographs of Stanford sports including football, baseball, basketball, track, golf, tennis, swimming. Where indicated, some albums contain clippings only.
Access Terms
Brandin, Alf E.; Eastman, Benjamin Bangs (Ben); Fleishacker, Herb; Grayson, Bobby; Harder, Theodore (Spud); Hoffman, Clifford (Biff); Hunt, Ernest Paul (Husky); Kerr, Andrew.; Lombardi, Frank; Luisetti, Hank.; Maloney, Henry Wilford.; Manning III, Elisha Archibald )Archie); Masters, Al; McCandless, John; McCreery, John H. (Hal); McDonald, Sam; Moffatt, Phil; Moscript, Monk; Nevers, Ernest Alonzo (Ernie); Norgard, Alvar Alfred; Packard, David, 1912-1996; Plunkett, Jim.; Rintala, Rudy; Schwartz, Marchmont H. (Marchy); Shipkey, Ted; Shove, Maynor; Simpkins, Bill; Smith, Roger (Podge); Smith, Rogers Philip (Podge); Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation.; Stanford University. Department of Athletics.; Taylor, Chuck; Templeton, Robert Lyman (Dink); Thornhill, Claude E.; Topping, Keith; Warner, Glenn S. (Glenn Scobey), 1871-1954; West, Clarence; Wilbur, Ray L., (Ray Lyman), 1875-1949; Baseball; Basketball--United States.; Boxing.; Football.; Golf--California.; Photoprints.; Swimming.; Tennis.; Track and field.
Collection Contents
- Photograph Albums
  - Volume 2, circa 1920-1926 (Box 1)
  - Volume 3, 1926-1927 (Box 1)
  - Volume 4, circa 1927-1928 (Box 1)
  - Volume 5, 1927-1929 (Box 2)
  - Volume 6, circa 1928 (Box 2)
  - Volume 7, circa 1930-1933 (Box 2)
  - Volume 8, circa 1928-1932 (Box 2)
  - Volume 9 - Football, 1929-1930 (Box 3)
  - Volume 10 - Football, Basketball, Golf, Track and Field, circa 1930s (Box 3)
  - Volume 10B - Football, 1930-1932 (Box 3)
  - Volume 11 - Golf, Tennis, Baseball, Track and Field, 1930-1931 (Box 3)
  - Volume 12 - Football, Track and Field, Baseball (clippings), 1928-1932 (Box 4)
  - Volume 13 - Football, Basketball, Swimming, Track and Field, Baseball, 1931-1935 (Box 5)
  - Volume 14 - Football, Track and Field, 1932-1933 (Box 5)
  - Volume 15 - Football, Basketball, 1935-1936 (Box 5)
  - Volume 16 - Football, 1938-1940 (Box 5)
  - Volume 17 - Track and Field, Golf, Tennis, Basketball, Baseball, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
  - Volume 18 - Football (Box 6)
  - Volume 19 - Football (clippings), 1940-1954 (Box 7)
  - Volume 20 - Football, 1941 (Box 8)
  - Volume 21 - Golf, Tennis, Basketball, Track and Field, 1941-1943 (Box 8)
  - Volume 23 - Football, 1941-1942 (Box 8)
  - Volume 24 - Football, 1947 (Box 8)
  - Volume 25 - Football, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Volume 26 - Football, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Volume 27 - Basketball (Box 9)
  - Volume 28 - Football, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
  - Volume 29 - Football, 1951 Fall (Box 10)
  - Volume 30A - Football, circa 1948-1949 (Box 10)
  - Volume 30B - Football, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Volume 31 - Swimming, Baseball, Golf, Tennis, Boxing, 1952-1953 (Box 10)
  - Volume 32 - Basketball, 1952-1957 (Box 10)
  - Volume 33 - Track, 1952-1954 (Box 11)
  - Volume 34 - Baseball, Golf, Swimming, Diving, circa 1950s (Box 11)
  - Volume 35 - Football, 1957-1958 (Box 11)
  - Volume 36 - Golf, Tennis, Swimming, Baseball, Track, 1953-1956 (Box 11)
  - Volume 37 - Football, 1953-1955 (Box 12)
  - Volume 38 - Football, 1955-1956 (Box 12)
  - Volume 39 - Baseball, 1957-1958 (Box 12)
  - Volume 40 - Track and Field, 1956-1958 (Box 12)
  - Volume 41 - Swimming, Golf, Tennis, 1956-1958 (Box 13)
  - Volume 42 - Basketball, Track and Field, circa 1950s (Box 13)
  - Volume 43 - Basketball, Track and Field, circa 1950s (Box 13)
  - Volume 44 - Football, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
  - Volume 45 - Basketball, 1959-1965 (Box 14)
  - Volume 46 - Olympic Track and Field, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Volume 47 - Tennis, circa 1960s (Box 14)
  - Volume 48 - Track and Field, circa 1961 (Box 14)
  - Volume 49 - Football, circa 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Volume 50 - Football, 1961-1962 (Box 15)
  - Volume 51 - Football, circa 1964 (Box 15)
  - Volume 52 - Boxing, Gymnastics, Soccer, Wrestling, 1965-1967 (Box 16)
  - Volume 53 - Football, 1965-1967 (Box 16)
  - Volume 54 - Tennis, Swimming, Water Polo, Golf, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
  - Volume 55 - Football, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Volume 56 - Track and Field, circa 1967 (Box 18)
  - Volume 57A - Football, circa 1967 (Box 18)
  - Volume 57B - Football, circa 1967 (Box 18)
  - Volume 58 - Football (clippings and programs), 1970 (Box 19)
  - Volume 59 - Coaches, Members of the Staff, Miscellaneous, circa 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Volume 60 - Rugby, Cheerleading, Band, circa 1967-1968 (Box 20)